orgsync.com 2011-11-24

# Privacy Policy | OrgSync

_In this document, 'OrgSync.com' and 'OrgSync' are property owned by OrgSync, Inc. and may be used synonymously with 'OrgSync, Inc.' where appropriate._

OrgSync knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our Privacy Policy. By visiting OrgSync.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

**What Personal Information About Users Does OrgSync Gather?**

The information we learn from users helps us personalize and continually improve your experience at OrgSync.com. Here are the types of information we gather. 

  1. **Information You Give Us:** We receive and store any information you enter on our website or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of certain of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future visits for you, improving our services, and communicating with you. 
  2. **Automatic Information:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many websites, we use "session variables," and we obtain certain types of information when your web browser accesses OrgSync.com. Unlike "cookies," "session variables" reside on our server and not on your computer. 
  3. **E-mail Communications:** We store all e-mail correspondences between you and OrgSync.com in order to improve your future experiences. 

**Does OrgSync Share the Information It Receives?**

Information about our users is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share user information only as needed and only as described below. 

  1. **Protection of OrgSync and Others:** We release account and other personal information when we believe release is required to comply with the law or a court order; to enforce or apply our Master Subscription Agreement; or protect the rights, property, or safety of OrgSync, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 
  2. **Agents:** We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include sending postal mail and e-mail and processing credit card payments. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. 
  3. **As part of our service:** OrgSync is a form of social network. As such, the information you supply may be used to help connect you with other similar members. Additionally, administrators of any organization you join have the option of making several of the components of your OrgSync enabled organization publicly accessible. Please check with your organization's administrators before you register if you are concerned that your activities within the club may be made public.
  4. **Business Transfers:** As we continue to develop our business, we might buy or sell business units. In such transactions, user information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy. Also, in the event that OrgSync, Inc., or substantially all of its assets are acquired, user information will be one of the transferred assets. 
  5. **Facebook Connect:** Orgsync does not send or share information with Facebook in any manner. Facebook is aware when someone logs in to OrgSync through Facebook Connect, but no user information is sent from OrgSync to Facebook. 

**How Secure Is Information About Me?**

  1. We work to protect the security of your information during transmissions by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software and randomized hashing. 
  2. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off and close the web browser when you are finished using the site. 

**Which Information Can I Access?**

OrgSync gives you access to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with OrgSync.com for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. 

**What Choices Do I Have?**

  1. You can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to take advantage of some of OrgSync.com's features. 
  2. 1.You can add, hide, remove or update certain personal information including email addresses, phone numbers, postal addresses, and memberships.

**Children**

OrgSync.com does not sell products or services for purchase by children. When products are suitable for use by children, they are intended as products and services for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use OrgSync.com only with the involvement of a parent or guardian or if you are an enrolled student of one of our customers. 

**Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions**

If you choose to visit OrgSync.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Master Subscription Agreement. If you have any concern about privacy at OrgSync.com, please contact us with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it.

Our business changes constantly and our Privacy Policy may change. You should check our website frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make. We will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of user information collected in the past; however, we reserve the right to make changes to this Policy and our practices.
